{
    "subject": "resource/John_William_Boone",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "John William Boone was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9153188467025757,
            "question": "Is John William Boone American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8930059671401978,
            "question": "Where was John William Boone born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7390540838241577,
            "question": "What period of history was John William Boone born into?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5885272026062012,
            "question": "Where did John William Boone likely grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5734168291091919,
            "question": "What country is John William Boone from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3743254542350769,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about John William Boone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3529179096221924,
            "question": "Do you know anything about John William Boone's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3314994275569916,
            "question": "What might be some interesting facts about John William Boone's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2982369661331177,
            "question": "What kind of impact did John William Boone have on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28424081206321716,
            "question": "Are there any notable events that happened during John William Boone's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John William Boone was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8930_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of impact did John William Boone have on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8930_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some interesting facts about John William Boone's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8930_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about John William Boone's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8930_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8930_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms John William Boone was indeed an American pianist and composer who lost his sight at six months old. The correct birthplace of John William Boone is also mentioned as being born in a federal militia camp near Miami, Missouri."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The provided documents mention that John William Boone was born in a federal militia camp near Miami, Missouri. Missouri is a state within the United States, supporting the statement that John William Boone was born in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}